<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Facebook Marketing</string>

    <string name="tip1">We know. Facebook isn’t new. And to say that every business needs a
        Facebook presence today would be an blatant understatement.

However, a lot has changed since Facebook first entered the marketing scene.
        Today, the world’s largest social network can do things many of us would never have dreamed of 10 years ago:
        host 360-degree videos, sell products via a chatbot, or even serve as a top news source for two-thirds of the population.
\n\n

     It’s not only the sheer number of people, but the amount of our attention Facebook owns.
        Globally, the average user spends 50 minutes per day with Facebook properties.
        Considering the average person sleeps 8.8 hours a day, that means one-sixteenth of our
        waking hours are spent with our eyes glued to the social network.
\n\n

      For many, Facebook is the internet. That said, is your business taking full advantage of it?

Pages are the gateway for businesses to market among this holy grail of users.
        A Facebook Page is a public presence similar to a personal profile, but allows
        fans to “like” the business, brand, celebrity, cause, or organization.
        Fans receive content updates from the Page on their News Feed, while the business is able to raise brand awareness,
        deploy and track advertising, collect detailed audience insights, and chat with users who seek customer service.
\n\n

       In the next page you’ll find everything website links to all the information you need to know to become a master Facebook marketer.
        If you are looking for facebook consultant click the consultancy option in the menu. In order to contact us click the email button
        No matter if your business has had a Page for years or you’re just getting started, this comprehensive guide is for you.\n\n


 </string>
    <string name="Admanager7"><a href="http://www.socialmediaexaminer.com/facebook-for-business-ultimate-facebook-marketing-guide/">Developer</a>  </string>

    <string name="Admanager"> www.socialmediaexaminer.com/how-to-set-up-an-effective-facebook-ad-campaign/</string>
    <string name="Link2">How do I create my first Facebook advertising campaign?click link below:</string>
    <string name="Link3"> www.socialmediaexaminer.com/facebook-ads-manager-guide-for-beginners/ </string>
    <string name="Link4"> How do I use Facebook Ads Manager?click link below:</string>
    <string name="Link5"> www.socialmediaexaminer.com/how-to-build-a-facebook-page-for-business-a-guide-for-beginners/ </string>
    <string name="Link6"> How do I make a business Facebook page? click link below: </string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
